待在原地
Stay where you are!
你们在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
丹尼尔  救命
Daniel, help!
我没做错什么
I've done nothing wrong!
托马斯  快跑
Thomas, run!
别伤害我的孩子们
Don't you hurt my kids!
科尔牧师
Reverend Cole.
拜托
Please.
是时候了  亨利
Time's come, Henry...
将奴隶制的罪恶从这片土地上冲走
For the sins of slavery to be washed away from this land.
由你手上的血来净化  这是上帝的旨意
Purged by blood from your hands as foreordained by god himself.
上帝
Lord.
发发慈悲
Have mercy.
只要有被奴役的人  我就与他们同在
For as long as there are those in bonds, I am bound with them.
离开这里
Leave this place!
你们自由了
You are free!
不  他们属于我
No, they're--they're mine!
我没有触犯法律
I have broken no law.
法律
Law?
我不承认任何尘世的主人  他们也不该承认
I acknowledge no master in human form, nor should they.
但如果要我放弃自己的生命
But if I be asked to forfeit my life
来为他们寻求公正
in furtherance of justice for them,
我很乐意让自己的双手
I will gladly mingle my blood
沾上被杀者之血
with that which I spill...
就在今晚
Tonight!
不要
No!
爸爸
Pa!
-执行旨意吧  -不要
- Let it be done! - No!
露丝
Ruth?
你做了什么
What'd you do?
她做了很多事
Oh, she did plenty.
你能照顾她吗
Will you tend to her?
-当然  -带走她
- Of course. - Take her.
她枪击了一个人
She shot a man.
-你就是法律  -我会处理的
- You're the law. - I'll handle it.
这还不够
That's not good enough.
教会的女士还真会开枪
Those church ladies sure can shoot.
闭嘴  我需要别人帮我抬他
Shut up. I need help with this man.
让他死吧
Let him die.
帕萨姆  德莱尼  来吧
Psalms? Delaney? Come on.
扶他起来
Get him up.
别管他  他不配活着
Leave him. He don't deserve to live.
他要是死了露丝就是杀人犯了
He dies, Ruth's a murderer.
把后面那张桌子腾出来
Clear off that back table!
早餐时间结束  各位
Breakfast is over, folks.
轻点轻点
Easy, easy, easy.
我说了轻点
Ahh! I said easy!
你需要什么  博汉南先生
What you need, Mr. Bohannon?
有伊娃在
We got Eva here.
你们回去干活吧
Get on back to work.
德莱尼  我们需要造好那台蒸汽挖土机
Delaney? Need that steam shovel built.
帕萨姆
Psalms.
子弹直接穿过去了
Bullet went clear through.
这颗还在他体内
This one's still in him.
我知道你不会把手伸进我身体里找子弹
Well, I know you ain't going fishing.
你知道个屁
You don't know shit.
他快失血过多了
He's bleeding out.
要是不把子弹取出来  他会死的
We don't get that bullet out, he gonna die.
我需要些咖啡渣
I need some coffee grounds.
有多少拿多少来
Much as you got.
他需要看医生
He needs a doctor.
我们不是在这吗
Well, he's got us.
-按住他  -混...啊...
- Hold him still. - Son of a--ahh!
如果不给我找医生  还不如给我找个牧师来
If you ain't got a doctor, you might as well find me a priest!
严格来说露丝只能算教堂工作人员  此处简翻为牧师
就是牧师开枪打的你
Closest thing we got put this bullet in ya.
上帝给予你生命  然后将之带走
The lord giveth and the lord taketh away!
露丝
Ruth.
你知道发生了什么事吗
Do you know what happened?
你知道这里是什么地方吗
Do you know where you are?
以斯拉已经入土...
Ezra's in the ground...
而我在报社办公室里
And I'm in the newspaper office.
你手上的火药一擦就掉
That gunpowder will wash right off.
我的手随我父亲
I have my father's hands.
你看
Look.
拿着
Here.
我给你拿条湿毛巾
I'll get you a wet cloth.
-给你  -没用的
- Here. - It won't help.
西德尼快失血致死了
Sidney's bleeding out.
他需要医生
Needs a doctor.
他死掉更好
He needs to be put down.
你就这么痛恨他吗
You that far gone?
这样对谁都好
It's what's best.
除了对露丝
For everybody but Ruth.
该死  波汉南
Damn it, Bohannon.
你去过墨西哥吗
Hey, you ever been to Mexico?
我靴子里有五美金
I got $5 in my boots.
我需要一把枪和一匹马
I need a gun and a horse.
可能需要两匹马
Maybe two horses.
我才不管你有五美金还是五千美金
I don't care if you've got $5,000.
反正你会死在这里  被人开枪打死或者被绞死
You're gonna die in this town, by bullet or by rope.
这么难搞  我喜欢
Hard to get. I like that.
他怎么样了
How is he?
还没死呢
He ain't dead yet.
拜托
Oh, come on.
我需要的是医生  不是会舞文弄墨的
I need a doctor, not some pencil dick.
给我听好  小混蛋
Listen to me, you little pissant.
你要想活过日落  我是你唯一的希望
I am your only hope of surviving past sundown,
所以我建议你  不要惹毛我
so my advice is: Don't piss me off.
天啊
Good God.
那是咖啡吗
Is that coffee?
打仗的时候我们用那个来止血
We used it in the war to slow the bleeding.
难怪你们输了
No wonder you lost.
情况有多严重
How bad?
子弹在下腹部
Bullet's lodged in the lower abdomen.
划破了腹腔动脉
It's nicked the celiac artery.
如果不把动脉缝合...
If I don't sew it up--
止住血的话
Stop the bleeding...
他就死定了
he won't need my help to die.
那就治好他
All right, fix it.
我可不是魔术师
I'm not a magician.
慢慢来吧
Let's get started, then.
我说了我撑不过去的
I told you I wasn't gonna make it.
行了吧西德  你也不是第一次中枪了
Oh, hell, Sid. You've been shot before.
很多次呢  这是你自己说的
Plenty a times, so you told it.
那是谎话
I lied.
我从没中过枪
I ain't never been shot.
按住他
Hold him!
我在努力
I'm trying.
快点
Hurry -- hurry up.
找到了
I got it.
快取出来
Okay, get it out. Get it out.
伊娃  给我拿个碟子来
Eva, get me a pan.
他了死吗
He dead?
还没
Not yet.
你看到了什么  露丝
What did you see, Ruth?
告诉我
Tell me!
你看到了什么  露丝
What did you see, Ruth?
对不起  爸爸
I'm sorry, papa!
对不起
I am sorry!
我不会再打你了
I won't strike you again.
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you saw.
我看到了那些人
I-I saw what happened...
出了什么事
to those men --
和你做的事
what you did.
那是上帝的意愿  露丝
It's god's will, Ruth...
因为那些人是罪人
'cause those men were sinners.
奴隶主
Slavers.
在堪萨斯散播他们的邪恶
Practicing that wickedness here in Kansas.
上帝需要通过我对这些人施以审判
God exacts judgment against such men through me,
我就是他手中的工具
the instrument of his hand.
这是上帝的意愿
It's god's will.
上帝的意愿
God's will?
这是什么
What is it?
上帝的意愿
God's will.
没错
That's right.
好孩子
Good girl.
她不对劲
She's not herself.
在战争中你一定见过这样的场景吧
I'm sure you've seen this in the war.
喝水
Water...
也冲不走嘴里那股金属味
won't chase the metal from your mouth.
有金属味是因为心跳过快
It's from your heart racing.
这是开枪杀人后的正常反应
It's what happens when you shoot a man.
你的手也很凉
And your hands get cold.
这种感觉会过去的
It'll pass.
我杀了那个人
I killed that man.
你谁也没杀
You ain't killed nobody.
杜兰特把子弹从西德尼身上取出来了
Durant dug the bullet out of Sidney.
现在在为他缝合伤口
He's sewing him up now.
他会为他犯下的罪受绞刑
He'll hang for what he done.
我们必须按法定程序来  博汉南先生
We will have due process, Mr. Bohannon.
由你亲手执行  以你胸前警徽之名
And by your hand, per that badge on your chest,
这是我们的约定
as we agreed.
她什么也没干
She ain't done nothing
同样情况下你我也会做出一样的选择
You or I would have done if circumstances were similar.
我要你拘留她  送她上法庭受审
I want her jailed and arraigned before the court.
西德尼·斯诺才是该进监狱的人
Sidney Snow needs to be jailed.
只要他身体允许  他就会因谋杀罪受审
Soon as he's able, he'll stand trial for murder,
被定罪  绞死  然后被人遗忘
be convicted, hanged, and forgotten.
但如果这之前他就死了
In the event he dies first,
那她就得负责
it must be seen that she's held accountable.
因为向西德尼·斯诺开枪拘留教会的女士
You arrest the church lady for shooting Sidney Snow,
恐怕你这临时州长也就当不下去了
that might be your last act as provisional anything.
她对你就这么重要吗
She means that much to you?
对整个镇子都很重要
Whole town.
派个守卫看着她  剩下就看上天的安排了
Post a guard 'til we see what providence brings.
终点站到了  夏安站
End of the line folks! Cheyenne!
最后一站  终点站啦
Last stop! End of the line!
如果是你是来找麻烦的  你最好赶紧走
If it's trouble you bring, you best keep walking.
里面有我们有很多人
We got our fill within.
我是专门解决麻烦的  夫人
Trouble's what I seek, madam...
比如迈克尔·麦克吉尼斯这样的
In the form of Michael Mcginnes.
你知道哪里能见到他吗
Would you happen to know where I might encounter him?
我听说他离开镇子了
I heard he left town.
那么
Well, now...
如果是他亲爱的表兄想见他呢
Suppose it's his dear ol' cousin who'd be asking.
你见过他吗
Would you have seen him then?
就算是耶稣本人来问我
I don't care if it's Christ himself asking.
我也没见过麦克吉尼斯  也不想见他
I haven't seen Mcginnes and I don't expect to.
你是个火爆的俏娘们  对吗
You're a fine bit of stuff, aren't ya?
我们去妓院找吧
The brothel, then.
这不是西部走廊
Well, if it isn't the ugliest mug
那个奇丑无比的人吗
west of the bleeding channel.
-约翰尼  -迈克尔
- Johnny! - Michael!
见鬼  你好吗
How the hell are ya? Oh!
饥饿  饥渴  想打架
Hungry, horny, itching to fight.
你一点都没变
You haven't changed a bit.
我以为你不会来了
Beginning to wonder you wouldn't show.
纽约和这里相隔遥远
Ah, miles of cathouses and saloons
路上有很多妓院和酒馆  迈克尔
between New York and here, Michael.
但这里是最好的  伙计
But none as fine as this establishment, boy.
女士们  这是我表兄  "阔少"约翰尼·舍伊
Ladies! This is me cousin, "Dandy" Johnny Shea,
这群罕见的保加利亚人是"死兔帮"成员
And this pack of rare Bulgarians are the dead rabbits.
"死兔帮"一般是爱尔兰和意大利移民的暴力帮派
欢迎  伙计们
Welcome, lads.
欢迎  我说
Welcome. Tell you what.
你们为什么不带他们上楼
Why don't you take them upstairs
好好欢迎一下他们来到夏安
and welcome them to Cheyenne properly.
-来吧  -好的先生
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
快  起来  我要跟我表弟聊聊
Go on, get up. I'll speak to me cousin.
真俏
Hell yeah.
迈克尔
So, uh, Michael.
提醒我一下
Remind me now,
我是为什么原因离开了纽约五岔路的妻儿
why I left me dan and wife in the five points
来到这个
to come out to this...
腐烂恶臭之地的
rotten stink hole.
我们要勒索  教训一些人
We're gonna extort some people, bash some heads,
还要给州长吃点皮肉之苦
and strong-arm the governor.
我的老天啊
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
见到你简直太棒了  迈克尔
It's grand to see ya, Michael.
我也很开心  伙计
It's great to see ya, boyo.
告诉我  他不会死
Tell me he ain't gonna die.
我已经给他止了血
I've stemmed the bleeding.
他已经稳定了
He's stable.
我给过你机会  女士
I gave you ten, senorita.
还记得吗
You remember that.
放下枪  西德
Drop the gun, Sid.
再见了  博汉南
Adios, Bohannon.
你应该了解我的
You know me better than that.
来  扶他上去
Here, get him up.
他撕裂了动脉
The artery's shredded.
我没办法了  我止不了血
I can't fix that and I can't stop the bleeding.
你不能让我就这么死了  医生
You ain't gonna let me die, Doc.
都到了这地步了
We come too far now.
没办法了  他完了
There's nothing more to be done, it's over.
该死
Shit!
好吧  锯掉
All right, saw it off.
从伤口上方锯  然后缝合
Right above the wound and sew it there.
你不是认真的吧
You can't be serious.
不  不许你锯掉我的腿
Hell no, you ain't gonna take my leg off!
我不能让你死  西德
Can't let you die, Sid.
锯掉腿吧
Leg's coming off.
博汉南
Bohannon!
你这样太残忍了  博汉南  让他死吧
Now you're just being cruel, Bohannon, let him die.
如果他死了  坎贝尔就要绞死露丝
He does, Campbell hangs Ruth.
别荒谬了  他不会绞死女人的
Don't be absurd. He can't hang a woman.
已经决定了
It's been done.
这地方没有一位陪审员会判她有罪的
There's not a jury in the land who'll convict her.
我可不想冒这个险
Yeah, well I ain't taking that chance.
有截肢刀吗
Got an amputation blade?
没有
No.
我也从来没有截过腿
And I have never amputated a leg, either.
我会帮你的
I'll get you through it.
你拿着那个刀最好是为了干别的
You best be building a birdhouse.
你想要死吗
You want to die?
我死也要四肢健全
If I do, it's gonna be with two legs on.
你放火时就注定没得选了
Well, you lost that choice when you threw them lanterns.
按住他
Hold him down.
别  别  别
Hey, hey, hey. No, no, no, hey!
别拿那刀靠近我  我发誓
You come anywhere near me with that knife, I swear it god,
不然你死定了
It's gonna be the last thing you do!
不要  不要
No! No no!
听着  博汉南  博汉南
Look! Hey, Bohannon! Bohannon!
看着我  看着我  松开放我走吧
Look at me! Look at me! Just let it loose and let me go!
给我一匹马就行
Just put me on a horse!
给我一匹马我就走  永远不回来
Put me on a horse and I-I'll go! I don't never come back!
你再也不会见到我了
You ain't never gonna see me again!
拜托了  拜托了
Come on! Come on!
听着  不要锯我的腿
Look! Just don't take my leg!
给我一匹马  我就走  再也不回来了
Just put me on a horse, I'll go, I'll never come back,
你再也不会见到我了  我发誓
You never gonna see me again, I swear to god!
不要锯我的腿
Don't take my leg!
我个人并不想
I take no pleasure
把教会的女士送上绞刑架
in the prospect of sending the church lady to the gallows.
但我们必须要这样做
But that is the task laid before us,
速战速决吧
be swift about it.
你的朋友  埃里森小姐  需要管一管了
Your friend, Miss Ellison, will need to be managed.
她见多识广
She's widely read
而且对我们的治理政策不满
and has been critical of our policies here.
法律面前人人平等  法官
The rule of the law applies to everyone, Judge.
执法从来就不是个愉快的差事
Task of enforcing it is not a pleasant burden.
我不是冷漠无情的人
I'm not entirely unsympathetic.
只是履行职责而已
Couched in the right language.
埃里森小姐交给我处理
I'll handle Miss Ellison.
坎贝尔
Campbell!
在你喝酒之前  先给我听好了
You'll give me your ears before you bend them elbows again.
这位是"阔少"约翰尼·舍伊
This is here "Dandy" Johnny Shea.
他是位硬汉
He's a hard man.
职业拳击手
A bruiser.
还是我母亲那边的堂兄弟
And a cousin on me mother's side.
从今天开始
And from this day forward,
他是这里的新业主
he is the new proprietor of this establishment
如果有人对此有意见的话
and any man who takes issue with that
可以直接来找我
can take it up with meself,
也可以直接找约翰尼
can take it up with Johnny,
还可以找我们的好友
or with one of our good friends here.
是这个懦夫在你手被绑的时候
Is this the coward who beat ya
打你的吗  迈克尔
when your hands were tied, Michael?
是的
It is.
小伙  想跟我过几招吗
You want to, uh, you want to dance with me, boyo?
他现在可帮不了你
He can't save you now.
赌场是你的了  麦克吉尼斯先生
Casino is yours, Mr. Mcginnes.
麦克吉尼斯先生  我们已经让出了赌场
Mr. Mcginnes, we conceded the casino.
约翰尼  够了
Johnny, that's enough.
我要把这烂东西从你头骨里抠出来
I'll scoop the shite clean out of your skull!
麦克吉尼斯先生  管好你的人
Mr. Mcginnes, control your man!
约翰尼
Johnny!
我说了停手  放他走
I said stop, let go of him.
我听见了  小米
I heard ya, mick!
问题是  我爱你
Thing is, I love ya,
但是我不为你工作
But I don't work for ya!
疯子
A madman.
他们就是这么称呼我父亲的
That's what they called my father.
谁  报纸上吗
Who? The newspapers?
我曾经很恨记者
I used to hate reporters.
我如今还是恨他们...
I still do...
有时候
sometimes.
当他离开家里
When he left home
开始致力于为印第安人发声
to speak for the Indians once and for good,
我读了描写他功绩的每一篇报道
I read every article on his exploits.
他们称他为殉道者
And they called him a martyr.
我不是个殉道者
I'm not a martyr.
你是怎么看自己的
How do you see yourself?
我是个母亲
I'm a mother.
这会疼死你的
This is going to hurt like hell.
不不不  不要  等等  等等
No no no no! No! Wait wait wait wait wait wait!
动手吧  博汉南
Now, Bohannon.
-求你了  伙计  -别动
- Come on, man. - Hold still.
这样会快一点
It'll go faster.
别把它切下来
Don't cut it off.
向你致以我的哀悼  露丝小姐
My condolences, Miss Ruth.
为了以斯拉的离世
Over Ezra passing.
谢谢你  帕萨姆
Thank you, Psalms.
你需要什么吗
What you need?
我去帮您拿
I'll get it for you.
不了  我只需要过去
No, I need to pass.
我在这里就是为了确保你留在原地
I-I'm here to see you stay put.
是博汉南先生的命令
Mr. Bohannon's orders.
那你能告诉我斯诺先生的情况吗
Well, can you tell me what's happening with Mr. Snow?
我听说博汉南先生在尽自己所能  救他一命
I hear Mr. Bohannon doing everything he can to save him.
救他一命
Save him?
为什么救
Why?
为了救你  露丝小姐
To save you, Miss Ruth.
我觉得你最好还是进屋去
I think it's best you go back inside, now.
假如有一天我躺上了那张桌子
If I'm ever on that table,
我希望你在身边
want you there.
假如你真躺上了那张桌子
If you're ever on that table,
我希望是我把你弄上去的
I hope I'm the one puts you there.
棺材里的不是埃兰
It wasn't Elam in that box.
你自己说的
You said so yourself.
埃兰想要我
Elam wanted me.
他本可以和我一起和平离开的
He would have left quiet with me.
而你夺走了这一切
And you took that from us.
伊娃...
Eva...
那是为了保护你
It was for your own protection.
没人求你保护我
No one asked you for it.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你没死
You ain't dead.
这一切都是为了看我被绞死吗
All this to see me hang?
不是
Nope.
首先  你要救下教会的女士
First you gonna save the church lady.
一个善举不能洗净我所犯下的一切罪恶
One good act ain't gonna wash away all the bad I've done.
我们这种人会变成什么样呢  博汉南
What becomes of men like us, Bohannon?
你觉得我们的结局会如何
Where do you suppose we end up?
不会好
Nowheres good.
那个混蛋会活下去吗
That bastard gonna live?
把他的腿锯掉了
Took off his damn leg.
那他会比以前更恶毒的
He gonna be meaner than before.
恶毒不了多久了
Not for much longer.
你安排了守卫看着我
You posted a guard.
我们把他的腿锯下来了
We took the leg off.
他会活下去的
He'll live.
他会为以斯拉的事受到惩罚的  露丝
He will answer for Ezra, Ruth.
但是我会为伤害他而受到惩罚吗
But will I answer for him?
你会被释放的
You'll be free.
我们会重建你的教堂
We'll rebuild your church.
你们无法补救我所失去的东西
You can't rebuilt what I lost.
你当外科医生可比我当农民强多了
You're a better surgeon than I was a farmer.
根据我对你仅有的一点了解  这说明不了什么
Well, from what little I know of you, that's not saying a lot.
我以前想当个眼科医生
I wanted to be an eye doctor.
研究眼科
Studied ophthalmology.
但我没有上完医学院
But I never finished medical school.
你知道吗
Did you know that?
"大佬"[医生]这个称呼
'Doc' is an affectation a--
只是我用来
An honorific title
给自己在铁路这行提升地位的假头衔罢了
I adopted to help me in the business of railroading.
你骗我的吧
You're shitting me.
我没有
I am not.
该死
Damn.
你觉得像我们这样的人
What you think is gonna...
以后会有什么结局
happen to men like us?
铁路建成之后
After she's built.
我将作为
Well, I will be remembered
建成越州铁路的人被人们铭记
as the man who built the transcontinental railroad.
但没人会记得你
You will not be remembered at all.
连我都不会记得
Not even by me.
感谢你如此直白
Thanks for sugarcoating it.
这是真的
It's the truth.
如果你命够长  就会发现我所说都是对的
You live long enough, you'll see I was right.
是啊
Yep.
我想在死前最后再看一眼这世界
I thought I'd see the world one last time before I die.
你走不远的
Won't get far.
天啊
God.
我看过一个联邦军队的小子爬了半英里
I saw this union boy once, crawl a half-mile.
腰以下什么都没有
Nothing from the waist down.
他最多17岁
He couldn't have been more than 17.
真是惨不忍睹
It's a hell of a sight to see.
没有腿的家伙  匍匐前进
A man with no legs, pulling himself along.
我追着他
I chased him...
直到他实在爬不动了  我一脚踩在他身上
'til he couldn't go no more and I pinned him with my foot.
跟他说  你急什么啊  小子
Said, "What's your hurry, boy?"
他开始翻他的外套
He started looking through his jacket right about then,
找一张照片
for a photograph.
他想最后再看一次他的妈妈
See, he wanted to see his momma one last time,
在他临死前
before he died.
我记得他恨不得把外套弄穿
I remember he dug all through that coat.
真的很拼命地找
He looked real hard.
一直求我帮他找
Kept begging me to help him find it.
我说  糟了  小子
I said, "Well, hell, boy.
照片可能在你裤兜里呢
That picture's probably in your pants pocket."
我大笑了一通
I had a good laugh.
我们都有自己的牵挂
We all got moments.
我杀的每个人都有自己牵挂的某人
Every man I ever killed got one someplace.
该死  西德
Damn, Sid!
我得去告诉教会的女士
I need to tell that church lady...
我从没打算伤害她的男孩
I never meant to hurt her boy.
闭嘴
Shut up!
我知道我们这种人都是这种结局  博汉南
I know it happens to men like us, Bohannon.
死在离家千里之外的地方
We end up far from home...
血肉模糊
covered in blood...
狼狈不堪
and shit.
孤独死去
We die alone.
我说闭上你的臭嘴
I said shut your damn mouth.
闭上你的臭嘴
"Shut your damn mouth."
有意思
That's funny.
西德
Sid?
我很开心
This pleases me much.
拥有一个珍视圣言的孩子
There's a--it is a blessing to have--
是一件幸福的事
to have a child who cherishes god's word.
你真是我的好...
You are my good--
可爱的好女儿
good and beloved daughter.
"不可杀人"
"Thou shalt not kill."
昨晚那些人
Those men last night...
是上帝派我惩罚他们所犯的罪孽
God sent me to them to, uh-- to avenge their sins.
"伸冤在我
"'vengeance is mine.
我必报应  主说"
I will repay,' saith the lord."
对  这是保罗对罗马人说的
Yeah. Paul to the Romans.
撒旦有时也会引用圣经
Satan himself does sometimes quote scripture.
这是他最邪恶的伎俩之一
It's one of his foulest tricks.
"不要自己伸冤
"Avenge not yourselves,
宁可让步  听凭主怒"
But rather give place unto wrath."
够了
Enough!
这些话是什么意思  爸爸
What does it mean, papa?
等你长大了
When you're older the--
真义自会揭示
The truth meanings will stand revealed.
所以主才让长老引导我们
That is why the lord puts our elders above us.
露丝
Ruth?
上帝不会通过他的造物复仇
God doesn't avenge sins through his creations.
他不会让人杀人
He doesn't move men to kill.
我见过的很多人
I've met plenty of men who would
都会颠覆你的这个想法
have you believe differently.
你不信赖上帝
You don't rely on god...
对吗  埃里森小姐
Do you, Miss Ellison?
没错
No.
为什么
Why?
我见过很多人以主之名犯下恶行
I've seen far too much of what men do in his name...
所以我难以相信上帝真的存在
to believe that he would ever be there for me.
埃里森小姐
Miss Ellison.
你确定要走这步吗
You sure you want to do that?
你确定要起诉露丝·科尔吗
Are you sure you want to prosecute Ruth Cole?
没有了西德尼·斯诺这种人
The world is a better place
这个世界会变得更好
without men like Sidney Snow,
而科尔女士这样道德高尚的女人也会让世界更好
And better with women of high moral standards like Miss Cole.
以及你
And yourself.
约翰  这不是回答
John, that's not an answer.
这是官方口吻
That's a public position.
我不是傻瓜  路易丝
I'm not a fool, Louise,
但是我是州长  这是有所意义的
But I am the governor and all that implies.
我能引用这句话吗
Can I quote you on that?
你不能
No, you cannot.
事实上
In fact...
我建议在此事尘埃落定前
I would suggest that until this matter resolves,
你不要在报纸上报道
You keep it out of the newspaper.
这是请求
Is that a request...
还是威胁
Or a threat?
公众的癔病可帮不了科尔女士
Public hysteria will not help Miss Cole's cause.
也帮不了你
Nor yours.
他这种人
He's better off.
死了更好
A man like that--
而我们这种人
Men like us...
仍然职责在身
We still got a job to do.
你知道你的职责是什么
You know what yours is.
我去把淤泥马车驶过来
I'll bring the muck wagon around.
我不是那个意思
That's not what I meant.
我知道你是什么意思
I know what you meant.
他死了  对吗
He's dead, isn't he?
本周被杀者  以斯拉[姓氏未知]  西德尼·斯诺
对不起  露丝
I'm sorry, Ruth.
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
也不是上帝的意愿
Or god's will.
我会想办法的
I'll figure a way out.
我很好  博汉南先生
I'm fine, Mr. Bohannon.
唯一一件比枪击斯诺先生更令我心满意足的事
The only thing more satisfying than shooting Mr. Snow,
就是听到你告诉我他的死讯
Was the moment you told me he was dead.